<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!DOCTYPE autoupdate_catalog PUBLIC "-//NetBeans//DTD Autoupdate Catalog 2.3//EN"
"https://netbeans.org/dtds/autoupdate-catalog-2_3.dtd">

<module_updates timestamp="09/00/19/20/07/2005">
  
  <license name="LICENSE_jse_nbm.txt"><![CDATA[Sun Microsystems, Inc. 
Binary Code License Agreement

READ THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT AND ANY PROVIDED SUPPLEMENTAL LICENSE TERMS 
(COLLECTIVELY "AGREEMENT") CAREFULLY BEFORE OPENING THE SOFTWARE MEDIA PACKAGE. 
BY OPENING THE SOFTWARE MEDIA PACKAGE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT. 
IF YOU ARE ACCESSING THE SOFTWARE ELECTRONICALLY, INDICATE YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF 
THESE TERMS BY SELECTING THE "ACCEPT" BUTTON AT THE END OF THIS AGREEMENT. IF 
YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF  THE TERMS, RETURN THE UNUSED SOFTWARE TO YOUR PLACE 
OF PURCHASE WITHIN 15 DAYS OF PURCHASE FOR A REFUND OR, IF THE SOFTWARE IS 
ACCESSED ELECTRONICALLY, SELECT THE "DECLINE" BUTTON AT THE END OF THIS 
AGREEMENT. 

1. 	LICENSE TO USE. Sun Microsystems, Inc. ('Sun") grants you a 
non-exclusive and non-transferable license for the internal use only of the 
accompanying software and documentation and any error corrections provided by 
Sun (collectively "Software"), by the number of users and the class of computer 
hardware for which the corresponding fee has been paid. 

2. 	RESTRICTIONS. Software is confidential and copyrighted. Title to 
Software and all associated intellectual property rights is retained by Sun 
and/or its licensors. Except as specifically authorized in any Supplemental 
License Terms, you may not make copies of Software, other than a single copy of 
Software for archival purposes. Unless enforcement is prohibited by applicable 
law, you may not modify, decompile, or reverse engineer Software. You 
acknowledge that Software is not designed, licensed or intended for use in the 
design, construction, operation or maintenance of any nuclear facility. Sun 
disclaims any express or implied warranty of fitness for such uses. No right, 
title or interest in or to any trademark, service mark, logo or trade name of 
Sun or its licensors is granted under this Agreement. 

3. 	LIMITED WARRANTY. Sun warrants to you that for a period of ninety (90) 
days from the date of purchase, as evidenced by a copy of the receipt, the media 
on which Software is furnished (if any) will be free of defects in materials and 
workmanship under normal use. Except for the foregoing, Software is provided "AS 
IS". Your exclusive remedy and Sun's entire liability under this limited 
warranty will be at Sun's option to replace Software media or refund the fee 
paid for Software. 

4.	DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY. UNLESS SPECIFIED IN THIS AGREEMENT, ALL EXPRESS 
OR IMPLIED CONDITIONS, REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES, INCLUDING ANY IMPLIED 
WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR 
NON-INFRINGEMENT ARE DISCLAIMED, EXCEPT TO THE EXTENT THAT THESE DISCLAIMERS ARE 
HELD TO BE LEGALLY INVALID. 

5. 	LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. TO THE EXTENT NOT PROHIBITED BY LAW, IN NO 
EVENT WILL SUN OR ITS LICENSORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOST REVENUE, PROFIT OR DATA, 
OR FOR SPECIAL, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, HOWEVER 
CAUSED REGARDLESS OF THE THEORY OF LIABILITY, ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THE 
USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE SOFTWARE, EVEN IF SUN HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE 
POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. In no event will Sun's liability to you, whether in 
contract, tort (including negligence), or otherwise, exceed the amount paid by 
you for Software under this Agreement. The foregoing limitations will apply even 
if the above stated warranty fails of its essential purpose. 

6. 	TERMINATION. This Agreement is effective until terminated. You may 
terminate this Agreement at any time by destroying all copies of Software. This 
Agreement will terminate immediately without notice from Sun if you fail to 
comply with any provision of this Agreement. Upon Termination, you must destroy 
all copies of Software. 

7. 	EXPORT REGULATIONS. All Software and technical data delivered under this 
Agreement are subject to US export control laws and may be subject to export or 
import regulations in other countries. You agree to comply strictly with all 
such laws and regulations and acknowledge that you have the responsibility to 
obtain such licenses to export, re-export, or import as may be required after 
delivery to you. 

8. 	U.S. GOVERNMENT RESTRICTED RIGHTS. If Software is being acquired by or 
on behalf of the U.S. Government or by a U.S. Government prime contractor or 
subcontractor (at any tier), then the Government's rights in Software and 
accompanying documentation will be only as set forth in this Agreement; this is 
in accordance with 48 C.F.R. 227.7202-4 (for Department of Defense (DOD) 
acquisitions) and with 48 CFR 2.101 and 12.212 (for non-DOD acquisitions). 

9. 	GOVERNING LAW. Any action related to this Agreement will be governed by 
California law and controlling U.S. federal law. No choice of law rules of any 
jurisdiction will apply. 

10. 	SEVERABILITY. If any provision of this Agreement is held to be 
unenforceable, this Agreement will remain in effect with the provision omitted, 
unless omission would frustrate the intent of the parties, in which case this 
Agreement will immediately terminate. 

11. 	INTEGRATION. This Agreement is the entire agreement between you and Sun 
relating to its subject matter. It supersedes all prior or contemporaneous oral 
or written communications, proposals, representations and warranties and 
prevails over any conflicting or additional terms of any quote, order, 
acknowledgment, or other communication between the parties relating to its 
subject matter during the term of this Agreement. No modification of this 
Agreement will be binding, unless in writing and signed by an authorized 
representative of each party. 

For inquiries please contact: Sun Microsystems, Inc. 4150 Network Circle, Santa 
Clara, CA 95054 



Sun Microsystems, Inc. 
Supplemental License Terms for Sun JavaTM Studio Enterprise 6 2004Q1


These terms and conditions ("Supplemental License Terms") for the Software are 
supplementary to, and are made part of this Agreement.  Capitalized terms not 
defined herein will have the meanings ascribed to them in the Binary Code 
License Agreement.  These terms will supersede any inconsistent or conflicting 
terms in the Binary Code License Agreement.  Section 1 ("License to Use") and 
Section 6 ("Termination") of the Binary Code License Agreement shall not apply 
to the Software described in these Supplemental License Terms, unless expressly 
provided below.  The component product supplemental terms contained in Parts 
II-III ("Component Product Supplemental Terms") will supersede any inconsistent 
or conflicting provisions of the general supplemental terms contained in this 
Part I ("General Supplemental Terms").

I.  	General Supplemental Terms:

1.0  	DEFINITIONS.

1.1	"Affiliated Company" means any entity: (a) which is owned 50% or more by 
you; or (b) over which you exercise management control; or (c) which is under 
common control with you; or (d) which owns 50% or more of your Company.

1.2	"Company" means your entire organization and as further defined in the 
Proof of License.

1.3	"Component Product" means those components of the Software that are 
offered separately in Sun's standard product lists.

1.4	"Employees" means all full-time employees of Company.

1.5	"Employee Base Count" means the number of your Employees.

1.6	"Employee Base License Fee" means the annual license fee per Employee 
owed in accordance with this Agreement and the Proof of License, and in 
accordance with Sun's then-current price lists.

1.7	"Paid-Up License Fee" means the non-refundable, non-contingent fee 
payable by you to obtain a license for a particular version of the Software, or 
for a particular version of certain Component Products.  

1.8	"Proof of License" means the collective set of documents authorized by 
Sun evidencing your payment of the fees for purchase of the license and service 
rights under this Agreement, including without limitation the Sun order 
confirmation, receipt, or right to use certificate.

1.9	"Server Platforms" means the bundled or co-packaged Java Enterprise 
System software as well as any and all additional software bundled with the 
Server Platforms and delivered to you as part of the Server Platforms.  

1.10	"Service Provider Use" means use of the Software such that certain 
functions of the Software are made accessible (but not by providing the Software 
itself or via outsourcing services) to your end users via an extranet deployment 
to your direct customers or suppliers where the manner in which such functions 
are accessed is consistent with, and only as described in the Software's 
documentation.  Notwithstanding the foregoing, provision of such services to 
other parts of Company or Affiliated Company(s) is expressly excluded unless the 
Employees in such organizations are included in the Employee Base Count.

1.11	"Software" as referred to in these Supplemental License Terms, shall 
refer to the accompanying software, documentation and error corrections, if any, 
provided by Sun.  Software as licensed under Sections 2.1, 2.3 or 2.7 of these 
Supplemental License Terms must be expressly provided for in the Proof of 
License.  "Software" as referred to in these Supplemental License Terms does not 
include Server Platforms.

1.12	"You" and "Your" (whether capitalized or not) shall mean Company and/or 
Affiliated Company.

2.0  	LICENSE GRANT

2.1	Annual License to Use.   Under the terms of your Proof of License, Sun 
grants you a non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited annual license for  your 
internal use of the Software on computer systems owned or leased by you and on 
your premises.  The registration process for the Software is provided in the 
installation guide.  

2.2	License to Evaluate.  Except as licensed under the terms of your Proof 
of License, Sun grants you a non-exclusive, non-transferable, royalty-free and 
limited license to use Software internally for evaluation purposes only, for a 
period of ninety (90) days following delivery of the Software. No license is 
granted hereunder for any other purpose, including any commercial or production 
use of the Software.  In relation to Software licensed under this Section 2.2, 
Sun is under no obligation to provide you with support, updates, error 
corrections or any other service.   Sections 4.0, and 5.0 of the General 
Supplemental Terms will not apply to Software being licensed under this Section 
2.2. The Software may contain a timebomb mechanism. You agree to hold Sun 
harmless from any claims based on your use of Software for any purposes other 
than those of internal evaluation.

2.3	Paid-Up License Grant.  Subject to your Proof of License, if you have 
paid the Paid-Up License Fee for a version of a specific Sun product(s) 
contained in the Software, Sun grants you a license to that version of that Sun 
product in accordance with the terms of Section 1 and Section 6 of the Binary 
Code License Agreement, notwithstanding any other terms of this Agreement to the 
contrary.  Sections 2.1, 3,  5.1, and 5.2 of the General Supplemental Terms 
shall not apply to any Software licensed under this Section 2.3, and Section 4.0 
shall not apply if you obtain your Paid-Up License in accordance with Section 
2.3.1 (Conversion from Subscription to Paid-Up License) and 5.3.2 below 
(Conversion Paid-Up License Fee).  Software licensed under this Section 2.3 may 
not be deployed for Service Provider Use, unless expressly permitted in the 
Proof of License.

2.3.1.	Conversion from Subscription to Paid-Up License.  Subject to your 
payment of the fee to convert to a Paid-Up License in Section 5.3.2 of the 
General Supplemental Terms, if you have paid annual license fees for three (3) 
consecutive years under Sections 5.1 and 5.2 of the General Supplemental Terms, 
you may continue to use the Software as it was then-deployed during your 
subscription, so long as such deployment of the Software subscription was 
consistent with the terms of this Agreement at the time of conversion, and 
provided that any further Service Provider Use of the Software shall 
discontinue.  You will be required to provide requested information as to how 
the Software was deployed during your subscription to update your Proof of 
License to reflect your Paid-Up License.
2.4	Software Use Restrictions.  Subject to your Proof of License, you may 
use the Software for the sole purpose of designing, developing and testing your 
applets and applications ("Programs").  To the extent that you are designing, 
developing and testing Programs for a particular version of the Java platform, 
any executable output generated by a compiler that is contained in the Software 
must (a) only be compiled from source code that conforms to the corresponding 
version of the OEM Java Language Specification; (b) be in the class file format 
defined by the corresponding version of the OEM Java Virtual Machine 
Specification; and (c) execute properly on a reference runtime, as specified by 
Sun, associated with such version of the Java platform..

2.5	Server Feature License.  The Server  Platforms are provided to you only 
for use in conjunction with the Software for the sole purpose of designing, 
developing and testing of applications intended to run on the Server Platform. 
Server Platforms may not be deployed in a production environment (whether 
internally or externally accessible) or used for production purposes, including 
without limitation deploying the Server Platforms to run your business.  If you 
wish to deploy the Server Platforms in a production environment (whether 
internally or externally accessible) or use them for production purposes, 
including without limitation deploying the Server Platforms to run your business 
, you must purchase separate and appropriate licenses for the Server Platforms.  
You may use the Server Platforms for the the limited purpose of testing, 
staging, or quality assurance of your Programs for subsequent deployment in a 
production environment.   These terms will supersede any inconsistent or 
confliciting terms in the BCL or Supplemental Terms and  will supersede any 
inconsistent or confliciting licenses contained within the Server Platforms.

2.6	Server Platform Sample Applications.  Server Platforms may include 
sample applications (including without limitation the Logistics) that are 
provided solely for reference purposes pursuant to the terms of this Agreement.  
The sample applications may not be redistributed unless expressly provided for 
in this Agreement.

2.7	License to Distribute Redistributables. Subject to your Proof of License 
and the terms of this Agreement, Sun grants you a non-exclusive, 
non-transferable, limited license to reproduce and distribute in binary form, 
those files identified as redistributable in the documentation for the Software 
("Redistributables"), provided that: (i) you distribute the Redistributables and 
related proprietary notices complete and unmodified, and only bundled as part of 
your Programs, (ii) you do not distribute additional software intended to 
supersede any component(s) of the Redistributables (unless otherwise specified 
in the documentation), (iii) if you are distributing Java applets and 
applications for a particular version of the Java platform, any executable 
output generated by a compiler that is contained in the Software must (a) only 
be compiled from source code that conforms to the corresponding version of the 
OEM Java Language Specification; (b) be in the class file format defined by the 
corresponding version of the OEM Java Virtual Machine Specification; and (c) 
execute properly on a reference runtime, as specified by Sun, associated with 
such version of the Java platform, (iv) the Redistributables are licensed in a 
manner that protects Sun's interests at least as well as this Agreement, and (v) 
you will defend, indemnify and hold harmless Sun and its licensors from and 
against any damages, costs, liabilities, settlement amounts and/or expenses 
(including attorneys' fees) incurred in connection with any claim, lawsuit or 
action by any third party that arises from the use or distribution of all 
software contained in your distribution.

2.8	Additional Restrictions.  You agree that, (i) if your Proof of License 
restricts use of Software or Component Product(s) to a number of designated 
CPU's, users or entries (meaning a single instance of a distinguished name 
including attributes associated therewith), you will not deploy the Software on 
more than that number of designated CPUs, exceed that maximum number of users or 
exceed the specified number of entries respectively, (ii) you may copy and use 
(but not modify) the header files and class libraries solely to create and 
distribute programs to interface with Software's APIs and only as expressly 
provided in the Software's documentation, (iii) unless otherwise specified, if 
Component Products are delivered with embedded or bundled software that enables 
functionality of the Component Product, you may not use such software on a 
stand-alone basis or use any portion of such software to interoperate with any 
program(s) other than the Software, (iv) Software may contain source code that 
is provided solely for reference purposes pursuant to the terms of this 
Agreement, (v) some portions of Software are provided with notices and/or open 
source licenses from other parties which govern the use of those portions, (vi) 
you may not publish or provide the results of any benchmark or comparison tests 
run on Software to any third party without the prior written consent of Sun, 
(vii) use of encryption technology contained within the Software is subject to 
all applicable governmental regulations of the United States of America and the 
country where the Software is deployed, (viii) you may not assign or otherwise 
transfer, by operation of law or otherwise, any of your rights or obligations 
under this Agreement without Sun's prior written consent, (ix) you may not sell, 
rent, loan or otherwise encumber Software, and (x) for the avoidance of doubt, 
the disclaimer of warranty and limitation of liability provisions in this 
Agreement shall apply to all Software in this distribution.

3.0  	TERM AND TERMINATION.  The term of this Agreement shall be for the one 
(1) year, and shall automatically renew for successive one (1) year terms unless 
either party provides written notice to the other of its intention not to renew 
at least ninety (90) days prior to the commencement of the next term.  You will 
remain obligated for all fees through the date of termination.  Either party may 
terminate this Agreement if the other party materially breaches this Agreement 
and fails to remedy that breach within thirty (30) days of receipt of written 
notice of material breach from the non-breaching party.  Sun may terminate this 
Agreement immediately if (i) you fail to pay an invoice when due, or (ii) any 
Software becomes, or in Sun's reasonable opinion is likely to become, the 
subject of a claim of infringement or misappropriation of any intellectual 
property right.  Upon termination, you will cease all use of the Software, 
delete all copies of all Software, and if requested by Sun, certify the 
destruction of all Software, and Sun shall not have any further obligations 
under this Agreement.

4.0  	SUBSCRIPTION SUPPORT.  Upon (a) payment of fees when due under Sections 
5.1 and 5.2 and subject to the registration requirement set forth in Section 2.1 
of these General Supplemental Terms, or (b) payment of fees when due under 
Section 5.3.1, you will be eligible to receive developer services in accordance 
with the respective program rules provided at 
http://www.sun.com/service/servicelist/, the terms of which are incorporated 
herein, which may include support, product updates, managed forums and 
specialized content.    All services offered may be subcontracted or assigned by 
Sun and are subject to Sun's then-current end of service life policies.   Such 
services must be received by you within the subscription year, and will expire 
at the end of that subscription year.

5.0  	FEES.

5.1  	First Year License Fee.  Upon commencement of this Agreement, a 
non-refundable, non-contingent base license fee for the first year of an amount 
equal to the Employee Base Count multiplied by the Employee Base License Fee 
shall be due prior to any obligations being incurred by Sun and prior to your 
exercise of any rights granted under Sections 2.1 and 4.0.

5.2  	Subsequent Annual License Fees.  Upon each anniversary of this 
Agreement, you will provide payment of an annual license fee of an amount equal 
to the Employee Base Count, as assessed on the anniversary date, multiplied by 
the then-current Employee Base License Fee.  Your Employee Base License Fee will 
not increase by more than an average of five percent (5%) compounded annually, 
as averaged over the product lifetime.

5.3  	Optional Paid-Up License Fee.  

5.3.1	Initial Paid-Up License Fees.  The Software or Component Product(s) may 
be licensed to you under the terms of this Agreement upon payment of Paid-Up 
License Fees in accordance with Sun's then-current standard published price 
lists available at that time for a paid-up license for the respective Sun 
product.  Developer services under Section 4.0 are included in the Paid-Up 
License Fee under this Section 5.3.1 for the first year.  Upon each anniversary 
of this Agreement, in order to continue receiving developer services, you must 
pay Sun a subsequent annual developer services fee in accordance with Sun's 
then-current standard published price lists available at that time.

5.3.2	Conversion Paid-Up License Fees.  If you have paid annual license fees 
for three (3) consecutive years under Sections 5.1 and 5.2 of these General 
Supplemental Terms, you may elect to pay Sun a Paid-Up License Fee equal to one 
point five times (1.5x) the then-current annual license fee for the Software.  
Payment of the Paid-Up License Fee under this Section 5.3.2 automatically 
converts the term of the Agreement to an unlimited time period solely for your 
then-currently deployed versions of the Software, subject to the Agreement 
termination provisions.

5.3.3	 Technical support services, maintenance services for upgrades and 
updates, professional services, architecture workshop services, training 
services, or installation services are not included in the Paid-Up License Fee 
under Section 5.3.2, and the delivery of any such services would be subject to 
Sun's then-current prices, terms and conditions.  

6.0 	REPORTING AND AUDIT. During the term of this Agreement and for five (5) 
years following termination of this Agreement, Sun shall have a right to audit 
your facilities and records from time to time in order to verify you compliance 
with the terms and conditions of this Agreement. Any such audit shall only take 
place during your normal business hours and upon no less than ten (10) days 
prior written notice from Sun.  Sun shall conduct no more than one such audit in 
any twelve-month period except for the express purpose of assuring compliance in 
such cases where non-compliance has been established in a prior audit. Sun will 
give written notice of any non-compliance, and if a payment deficiency exists, 
then you shall have fifteen (15) days from the date of such notice to make 
payment to Sun for any payment deficiency. The amount of the payment deficiency 
will be determined by multiplying the underreported number of Employees, as of 
the anniversary date of this Agreement, by the Employee Base License Fee.  If 
Sun determines that the underreported number of Employees exceeds five percent 
(5%) of the represented number of Employees, then in addition to the payment 
deficiency, Sun may recover from you the costs of the audit, and interest 
charges for the payment deficiency at the lesser of 1.5% per month or the 
highest rate allowable by law.

7.0  	JAVA TECHNOLOGY.  The following terms apply to Java technology 
components contained in the Software ("Java Technology").

7.1. 	Java Technology Restrictions.  You may not modify the Java Platform 
Interface ("JPI", identified as classes contained within the "java" package or 
any subpackages of the "java" package), by creating additional classes within 
the JPI or otherwise causing the addition to or modification of the classes in 
the JPI. In the event that you create an additional class and associated API(s) 
which (i) extends the functionality of the Java platform, and (ii) is exposed to 
third party software developers for the purpose of developing additional 
software which invokes such additional API, you must promptly broadly publish an 
accurate specification for such API for free use by all developers. You may not 
create, or authorize your licensees to create, additional classes, interfaces, 
or subpackages that are in any way identified as "java", "javax", "sun" or 
similar convention as specified by Sun in any naming convention designation.

7.2 	SOFTWARE UPDATES FROM SUN. You acknowledge that at your request or 
consent optional features of the Software may download, install, and execute 
applets, applications, software extensions, and updated versions of the Software 
from Sun ("Software Updates"), which may require you to accept updated terms and 
conditions for installation. If additional terms and conditions are not 
presented on installation, the Software Updates will be considered part of the 
Software and subject to the terms and conditions of the Agreement.
7.3 	SOFTWARE FROM SOURCES OTHER THAN SUN. You acknowledge that, by your use 
of optional features of the Software and/or by requesting services that require 
use of the optional features of the Software, the Software may automatically 
download, install, and execute software applications from sources other than Sun 
("Other Software"). Sun makes no representations of a relationship of any kind 
to licensors of Other Software. TO THE EXTENT NOT PROHIBITED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT 
WILL SUN OR ITS LICENSORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOST REVENUE, PROFIT OR DATA, OR FOR 
SPECIAL, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, HOWEVER CAUSED 
REGARDLESS OF THE THEORY OF LIABILITY, ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THE USE OF 
OR INABILITY TO USE OTHER SOFTWARE, EVEN IF SUN HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE 
POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

8.0  	limitation of liability.  The following sentence shall replace the 
second sentence of Section 5 "Limitation of Liability" in the Binary Code 
License portion of this Agreement:  "In no event will Sun's liability to you, 
whether in contract, tort (including negligence), or otherwise, exceed the 
annual license fees last paid by you for the Software under this Agreement."

9.0 	Trademarks and Logos.  You acknowledge and agree as between you and Sun 
that Sun owns the SUN, SOLARIS, JAVA, SUN ONE, trademarks and related 
trademarks, service marks, logos, trade dress and other brand designations ("Sun 
Marks"), and you agree to comply with the Sun Trademark and Logo Usage 
Requirements currently located at http://www.sun.com/policies/trademarks. You 
agree not to: (a) challenge Sun's ownership or use of Sun Marks; (b) attempt to 
register any Sun Marks or any mark or logo substantially similar thereto; (c) 
remove, alter or add to any Sun Mark; (d) co-brand or co-logo your products with 
any Sun Marks; or (e) incorporate any Sun Marks into your trademarks, product 
names, service marks, company names, domain names or any other similar 
designations. Any use you make of the Sun Marks inures to Sun's benefit. 

10.0  	SERVICE PROVIDER USE.  You will defend and indemnify Sun and its 
licensors from and against any damages, costs, liabilities, settlement amounts 
and/or expenses (including attorneys' fees) incurred in connection with any 
claim, lawsuit or action by any third party that arises from your Service 
Provider Use of Software.





Component Product Supplemental Terms


Component Product Supplemental Terms are provided for the following products.  

II.  	Java 2 Standard Edition 1.4.1
III.	Sun ONE Application Server 7 Standard Edition, Update 1



II.  	Java 2 Standard Edition 1.4.1

The following Component Product Supplemental Terms additionally apply to the 
Java 2 Standard Edition 1.4.1 ("J2SE"), portions of Software.

1.0  	LICENSE GRANT.  The license grants set forth in the General Supplemental 
Terms, Sections 2.1 and 2.3 are granted for J2SE for the sole purpose of 
designing, developing, testing, and running your Progams intended to run on 
Java-enabled general purpose desktop computers and servers ("J2SE Programs").

2.0  	Java 2 Standard Edition Redistribution.  The J2SE software may be 
redistributed in its entirety under the terms of the General Supplemental Terms, 
Section 2.7 and the Part II of the Component Product Supplemental Terms, Section 
1, provided that the following additional conditions are met:  (i) you 
distribute J2SE complete and unmodified and only bundled as part of, and for the 
sole purpose of  running your J2SE Programs, and (ii) the J2SE Programs add 
significant and primary functionality to J2SE.

III.	Sun ONE Application Server 7 Standard Edition, Update 1 

The following Component Product Supplemental Terms additionally apply to the Sun 
ONE Application Server 7 Standard Edition, Update 1  ("AS") portions of 
Software.

1.0  	AS FOR EVALUATION ONLY.   You may use AS only under the evaluation 
license under Section 2.2 of these Supplemental License Terms and under the 
design, development and testing license under Section 2.4 of these Supplemental 
License Terms.  Use of AS for production purposes requires the separate purchase 
of an AS license.  AS may contain a time out mechanism. 


]]></license>
</module_updates>
