Hi, this video demonstrates how to get a Git project by cloning an existing Git repository from  GitHub using NetBeans IDE.
Before starting to clone a Git repository you need to ensure that you have a GitHub account, you are a GitHub project member,
and you know a Git repository URL.For non-automated SSH access, you need to have a private SSH key in the OpenSSH format
and a passphrase.For automated SSH access, you need to correctly configure SSH-agent or Pageant.
In NetBeans IDE, choose Team > Git > Clone from the main menu.
The Clone Repository wizard displays.
Specify the GitHub repository URL.
Enter git in the Username field.
Select the Private/Public Key option.
Click Browse to get to your personal key location.
Click Open.
Enter the passphrase.
Note that if using Pageant both the fields are left empty.
As soon as the IDE gets authenticated access to the GitHub server, the Remote Branches page of the wizard displays.
Click Next to continue.
Select the repository branch (or branches) to be downloaded to your local repository.
Click Next.
At the Destination Directory page, modify the pre-filled options if required.
Note that origin is a recommended value as an alias of the repository being cloned.
To activate after-scanning right after the clone finishes, leave the Scan for NetBeans Projects after Clone option selected.
Click Finish.
After the repository is cloned, the Clone Completed message displays.
Click Open Project to view the cloned project.
The IDE opens a valid NetBeans project from the cloned repository in the Projects window.
Git actions are now available from the context menu and main menu for the cloned project.
In this video you learnt how to clone a Git project from a remote server via the SSH protocol.
Thank you for watching.