Hi, this screencast demonstrates how to set upNetBeans IDE support for Oracle Java ME SDK8 Early Access on Windows.
To enable support for Oracle Java ME SDK 8 EAin NetBeans IDE, you need to:
download and install NetBeans IDE 8.0 Betafrom the NetBeans download page,
download and install Oracle Java ME SDK 8 EAfrom the Java ME SDK download page,
activate Java ME support inside the IDE,
and register Oracle Java ME SDK in NetBeansIDE.
Please note that it is strongly recommended touse JDK™ 8 Early Access.
After you've downloaded and installed the Allbundle of NetBeans IDE from the Netbeans IDEdownload page,
go to the Java ME SDK download page,
click the Accept License Agreement option,
download the installer file, and save it to anylocation on your computer.
Double-click the installer file to run the installer,and follow the instructions.
To activate Java ME support in the IDE,
complete the following steps:
Choose Tools > Plugins from the main IDE'stoolbar.
In the Plugins dialog box, click the Installed tab.
Select Java ME from the list of availablefeatures.
Click Activate.
At the Welcome panel of the Installer dialog
box, click Activate.
When the activation is successfully completed,
click Finish.
The icon for the plugin in the left pane reflects
the new status of the feature.
Click Close to close the Plugins dialog box.
To register the Oracle Java ME SDK 8 EA as a
platform in NetBeans IDE, complete the
following steps:
In the IDE, choose Tools > Java Platforms.
The Java Platform Manager dialog box displays.
Click Add Platform.
In the Select Platform Type panel of the Add
Java Platform wizard, select Java ME CLDC
Platform Emulator and click Next.
Select the directory you installed the Java ME
SDK 8 EA Platform to and click Open.
Ensure Java ME SDK 8 EA is chosen and click
Next.
As soon as the IDE detects the platform, click
Finish.
The Oracle Java ME SDK 8 EA is now
registered in Netbeans IDE.
Click Close.
To create a Java ME 8 Embedded Project, you
need to do the following:
Choose File > New Project.
In the New Project dialog box, select Java ME
Embedded in the Categories list and Java ME
Embedded Application.
Click Next.
In the Name and Location panel of the New
Project wizard, specify your project name and ensure that Java ME 8 EA Platform is chosen.
Please note that it is strongly recommended to
use JDK 1.8 EA, from which the tools like javac
or javadoc will be used.
Click Finish.
The IDE creates a new Java ME Embedded
application project.
To customize a Java ME 8 embedded project,
you can complete the following:
Right-click the project name and select
Properties in the context menu.
Choose Platform in the Project Properties dialog
box.
On this panel, you can specify the target JDK
and Java Micro Edition platform for your project.
You can also customize the devices used when
running the project, Java ME configuration,
profile, and optional packages
to extend the runtime environment.
The Application Descriptor category allows for
configuring such Java ME specific information as
attributes that are written to the application's
JAD file and JAR's manifest,
a list of MIDlets in the Suite,
Push Registry,
and API Permissions.
The Signing category enables you to sign a Java
ME application with the selected certificate.
On the Obfuscating panel, ProGuard can be
used to make code more difficult to read for
humans
when they try to reverse engineer an application.
The Run category depends on the selected
project's configuration.
It comprises command line options which are
passed to a device when running the application,
the Run method that is a way of deploying built JAR or JAD onto an emulator or a device
in a regular way or via OTA which means that a JAD file is exposed via an http link,
which the device uses to download JAD and run
the application.
Click OK to close the dialog box.
To run a Java ME 8 Embedded project in the
IDE, standard actions from the NetBeans toolbar
or context menu are used.
Right-click the project name and choose Run
from the context menu.
When you run your application, the IDE
compiles and builds the application according to
the project settings.
When you run your application, the IDE
compiles and builds the application according to
the project settings.
The output is shown in the device emulator as
well as in the Output window of the IDE.
Thank you for watching.