<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE rss PUBLIC "-//Netscape Communications//DTD RSS 0.91//EN" "http://my.netscape.com/publish/formats/rss-0.91.dtd">
<rss version="0.91">

<channel>
  <title>NetBeans Highlights</title>
  <description>A selection of news highlights, current newsletters and featured articles from netbeans.org, opensource IDE and application backplane</description>
  <link>http://netbeans.org/index.html</link>
  <language>en</language>
  <webMaster>webmaster@netbeans.org (NetBeans webmaster)</webMaster>
  <image>
    <title>NetBeans Highlights</title>
    <url>http://netbeans.org/images_www/v5/nb-logo.gif</url>
    <link>http://netbeans.org/index.html</link>
    <width>110</width>
    <height>30</height>
  </image>
  <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 18:10:02 +0100</pubDate><!-- #TIMESTAMP# -->

    <item>
    <title>31 May 2016: NetBeans Day in London</title>
    <link>https://blog.idrsolutions.com/2016/03/tickets-now-available-free-uk-netbeans-day/</link>
    <description>Join NetBeans users all over the UK in London and learn about the latest NetBeans features while networking and getting to know others in this free event.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>31 March 2016: NetBeans Day in Munich</title>
    <link>https://www.eventbrite.com/e/netbeans-day-germany-tickets-22323978621</link>
    <description>Come to NetBeans Day in Munich, Germany, and meet great speakers and other NetBeans users, including Adam Bien, Jaroslav Tulach, and many others!</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>17 February 2016: NetBeans Day Netherlands</title>
    <link>https://pidome.org/info/events/2016/2/17/netbeans-day-netherlands-februari-2016.html</link>
    <description>Free: Adam Bien, microservices, workshops, JavaScript, Java, and more! Join the latest NetBeans Day in the Netherlands.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>NetBeans Community Approves NetBeans IDE 8.1 for Release</title>
    <link>http://netbeans.org/community/news/index.html#1635</link>
    <description>We are pleased to announce the results of the NetBeans IDE 8.1 Community Acceptance Survey that ended November 2nd: 85% of 89 respondents agree that NetBeans IDE 8.1 Release Candidate is stable enough to be shipped! A few respondents pointed out several serious issues. We evaluated them all not to overlook some important problem. We have noticed that majority of web programmers appreciate improved generic support for JavaScript development like enhanced Node.js support, debugging, inspection and especially testing and packaging so our investment into this area paid off. Another success worth mentioning is big (98%) satisfaction with redesigned Java Profiler. Check it out yourselves!

Overall, this is a good news for the NetBeans IDE 8.1 from the community, and we thank all who provided this valuable feedback!</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Build with NetBeans IDE, Deploy to Oracle Java Cloud Service</title>
    <link>http://www.oracle.com/technetwork/articles/java/enterprise-cloud-2227135.html</link>
    <description>Save time and effort deploying applications. Learn to set up Oracle Java Cloud Service, then install and use the Oracle Cloud plugin in the NetBeans IDE.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Build a Rich Client Platform To-Do Application in NetBeans IDE</title>
    <link>http://www.oracle.com/technetwork/articles/java/rcp-todo-2194057.html</link>
    <description>Practice using NetBeans IDE features that improve code quality and increase developer productivity.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Video: Installing and Using Java ME SDK 8.0 Plugins in NetBeans IDE</title>
    <link>http://netbeans.org/kb/docs/javame/nb_me_plugins_screencast.html</link>
    <description>This screencast demonstrates installation and usage of Oracle Java ME SDK 8.0 Plugins in NetBeans IDE on the Windows operating system.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title> NetBeans 8: Support for Java 8, HTML5 and Beyond</title>
    <link>http://www.infoq.com/news/2014/04/netbeans8</link>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>NetBeans IDE 8.0 and New Features for Java 8</title>
    <link>http://www.javacodegeeks.com/2014/03/netbeans-ide-8-0-and-new-features-for-java-8.html</link>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>New Version of Free, Open Source NetBeans IDE Features Java 8 Support</title>
    <link>http://adtmag.com/articles/2014/03/26/netbeans-8-release.aspx</link>
  </item>


</channel>
</rss>

