Hi, this screencast demonstrates how toinstall Java ME SDK plugins into NetBeansIDE
and utilize advanced tooling of the Java ME 8platform.
Before installing Java ME SDK plugins intoNetBeans IDE, please, make sure that thefollowing prerequisites have been completed:
Java ME SDK is installed on your machine,
Java ME support is activated in NetBeansIDE,
and Java ME SDK is registered in the IDE.
You may want to watch the Video of NetBeansIDE Support for Java ME 8 at netbeans.org fordetails.
To install Java ME SDK plugins into NetBeansIDE, you need to
download the Oracle Java ME SDK 8 Pluginsfor NetBeans file from the Java ME SDKdownload page,
unpack the file to a directory on your machine,
launch NetBeans IDE and use NetBeansPlugins manager.
After you've downloaded and unpacked theOracle Java ME SDK 8 Plugins for NetBeansfile,
complete the following steps to install theplugins into NetBeans IDE:
In NetBeans IDE, choose Tools > Pluginsfrom the main IDE's toolbar.
In the Plugins dialog box, click the Settingstab.
Click Add to display the Update CenterCustomizer dialog box.
In the Name field, enter Java ME SDKPlugins.
Leave the Check for updates automaticallyoption selected.
In the URL field, use the file command topoint to the location where you haveunpacked your plugins.
Click OK to add the Java ME SDK Pluginsupdate center to the Settings tab.
Ensure the Java ME SDK Plugins updatecenter is selected and choose the AvailablePlugins tab.
Select Java ME SDK Tools and Java ME SDKDemos and click Install.
At the Welcome panel of the Installer dialogbox, click Next.
Review the license agreement, click theacceptance checkbox, and click Install tobegin the installation.
When the installation is successfullycompleted, leave the Restart IDE now optionselected, and click Finish.
After the IDE restarts, you need to make surethe plugins you have installed are active.
Choose Tools > Plugins to display thePlugins manager.
Click the Installed tab,
select the Show details option and scroll tofind the Java ME SDK Demos and Java MESDK Tools plugins in the list.
The green icon for the plugin to the leftreflects the active status of the plugin.Click Close to close the Plugins manager.
After both the plugins are installed, you cantake a look at Java ME Platform SDK sampleprojects
which highlight some of the technologies andAPIs that are supported by the emulator.
Choose File > New Project.
In the New Project dialog box, expand theSamples category and choose Java ME SDK8.0.
Java ME sample applications display in theProjects list on the right.
Select DataCollection Demo and click Next.
In the Name and Location page of the wizard,accept the default values for the project name,location, et cetera and click Finish.
The DataCollectionDemo project is createdand opened in the IDE.
Let's run the project using the Java ME SDKemulator from the Java ME SDK Tools plugin.
The plugin integrates Java ME utilities into thestandard NetBeans IDE menus.
For example, the Tools > Java ME menu is theplace to launch a set of tools including theDevice Selector.
The IDE displays the Device Selector window
where all available devices simulated by theJava ME SDK emulator are grouped byplatform.
Each subnode represents an emulator skinfor a device.
EmbeddedDevice1 and EmbeddedDevice2are two instances of a CLDC device.
They have identical capability sets but uniquephone numbers, making it easy to testcommunication between two devices.
You can double-click any device node to openthe Device Information tab in the IDE
and view such device details as supportedruntimes and extensions.
Right-click on a device and select theDataCollectionDemo project to run from thecontext menu.
In this demo, several data collector IMletsread data from peripheral devices
using the Device I/O API and send the data to a data processor.
Select all the Imlets to run and click OK.
Click Output to see the details of running yourapplication.
As an alternative you can choose Window >Output in the IDE.
When you are done, click Stop and close thedevice emulator.
The Java ME SDK Tools plugin enables you touse common profiling tasks, such as CPU,memory or network profiling.
The plugin also integrates the Java MEtooling into the Profiler > Java ME menu,
which is the place to work with the MemoryMonitor and Network Monitor.
To start a profiling session, right-click theDataCollectionDemo project and chooseProfile.
In the Profile dialog box, leave CPU Profilerselected and click Run.
The emulator opens with theDataCollectionDemo application running.
Run the IMLets, interact with the applicationas needed, and exit the application.
The IDE displays the profile data in the CPUsnapshot window.
Click the Info tab to view the summary of thesession.
The data collected during the emulationsession can be saved for future reference.
Well, that's all for the screencast.
Thank you for watching.